fastpitchnetworking.com 2008-12-17

# Fast Pitch

Last Updated: Janurary 2, 2007 

Your privacy is our top concern. We work hard to earn and keep your trust, so we adhere to the following principles to protect your privacy:

• Any sensitive information that you provide will be secured with all industry standard protocols and technology 

Notice of all changes that materially affect ways in which your personally identifiable data may be used or shared will be posted in updates to our Privacy Policy. If you continue to use the Fast Pitch! after notice of changes have been sent to you or published on our site, you hereby provide your consent to the changed practices

Please read this privacy policy to learn more about:  
1\. What personally identifiable information of yours is collected by Fast Pitch!   
2\. How the information is used.   
3\. With whom the information may be shared.   
4\. How you can access and change your Account information.   
5\. What security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information collected by Fast Pitch!.   
6\. How to contact us. 

**Information Collection**

**Registration:**  
In order to become a Fast Pitch! user, you must first create an account on this web site. To create an account you are required to provide the following contact information: name, email address, country, ZIP/postal code, a brief summary of your company, an overview of your competitive advantages, your ideal customers, ideal partners, possible future business purchases and choose a password.

**Profile Information:**  
Once a user, you may provide additional information to your account including recent press, events you are promoting or attending and more. Providing additional information beyond what is required at registration is entirely optional, but enables you to better promote your business and find new opportunities within the Fast Pitch! system.

**Information about your Contacts**  
In order to invite others to connect with you directly on Fast Pitch!, you will enter their names and email addresses (we also provide a contact upload form for bulk invites – see below). This information will be used by Fast Pitch! to send your invitation to connect on Fast Pitch!. 

You may also choose to manually enter or upload data about your contacts into the private “My Connections” section of our website. All information entered there will only be viewable by you and will not be searchable by others in the Fast Pitch! network without your permission.

All information that you enter or upload about your contacts will be covered by the same terms of this privacy policy as cover your own personally identifiable information.

**Cookies & Log Files:**  
Like most web sites, Fast Pitch! uses cookies and web log files to track site usage. A cookie is a tiny data file which resides on your computer which allows Fast Pitch! to recognize you as a user when you return to our site using the same computer and web browser. Unfortunately, if your browser settings do not allow cookies, you will not be able to use our website. Like the information you enter at registration or in your Profile, cookie and log file data is used to customize your experience on the web site.

One type of cookie, known as a “persistent” cookie, is set once you’ve logged in to your Fast Pitch! account. The next time you visit the Fast Pitch! web site, the persistent cookie will allow us to recognize you as an existing user so you will not need to log in before using the service. In order to access or change any of your private information (like a credit card number), however, you must log in securely again with your password even if your computer contains your persistent cookie. Additionally, if you log out of the Fast Pitch! site you will need to re-enter your password the next time you visit in order to log in to your account. Another type of cookie, called a “session” cookie, is used to identify a particular visit to the Fast Pitch! site. Session cookies expire after a short time or when you close your web browser.

Due to the communications standards on the Internet, when you visit the Fast Pitch! web site we automatically receive the URL of the site from which you came and the site to which you are going when you leave Fast Pitch!. We also receive the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer (or the proxy server you use to access the World Wide Web), your computer operating system and type of web browser you are using, as well as the name of your ISP. This information is used to analyze overall trends to help us improve the Fast Pitch! service. The linkage between your IP address and your personally identifiable information is never shared with third-parties without your permission or except when required by law.

**Viewing Other Activiy on Your Profile**  
Fast Pitch! offers our Platinum Members the ability to view who has recently visited their profile. The service, in the spirit of business networking, allows them the unique ability to reach out to someone who may have an interest in their product or service. Similar to walking into a ‘storefront’, the Platinum Member has the ability to reach out to the ‘customer’ and offer their assistance. 

**Web Beacons:**  
We may allow other companies (although not presently), called ad networks, to serve advertisements to Fast Pitch! users. Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors and research firms. Fast Pitch! may “target” some ads to users that fit a certain general profile — for example, “web designers looking for accountants in Tampa, FL.” 

To deliver these ads properly, Fast Pitch! may include a file, called a web beacon, from these ad networks within pages served by Fast Pitch! so the networks may provide anonymized, aggregated auditing, research and reporting for advertisers as well as to target ads to you while you visit other websites.  
Because your web browser must request these advertisements and web beacons from the ad network’s servers, these companies can view, edit or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site.

These general targets may also be used by ad networks to display targeted ads on other websites as a substitute for random, irrelevant ads. You will never see additional ads as a result of being a Fast Pitch! user and Fast Pitch! never provides personally identifiable information to any advertiser nor any third party.

**Children:**

Children are not eligible to use our service and we ask that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us or use the service.

**Information Use**  
Fast Pitch! is an online and offline service committed to helping professionals network and market their business effectively at one centralized location. The personally identifiable information you choose to provide on this site is used to help you describe yourself and your company to others. Other information, that does not personally identify you as an individual, is collected by Fast Pitch! Brands, LLC from the site (such as, by way of example, patterns of utilization) and is exclusively owned by Fast Pitch!. This information can be utilized by Fast Pitch at its sole discretion.

**Fast Pitch! Communications:**  
Fast Pitch! will communicate with you through email, direct mail, telephone, mobile phone, IM and fax. These may include a series of promotional and informative emails regarding new features and services provided by Fast Pitch!. Please be aware that you will always receive certain emails from Fast Pitch! related to the proper functioning of your account, such as email notices when another user requests to connect with you. Fast Pitch! may send you promotional information unless you have opted out of receiving such information. 

**Customized Content:**  
Information you provide at registration or in your Profile section is also used to customize your experience on the web site. For example, when you login to your account we may partial information about you and your company on our homepage when people log-in. The intent (obviously) is to provide you with immediate and maximum exposure opportunities. 

Additionally, many users upload third-party logos to their profiles, press releases and more. Fast Pitch! neither endorses nor is affiliated with most of these third-party companies. In most cases, Fast Pitch! is not affiliated with these companies. If a company feels the logo placed on a profile is in violation of their trademark guidelines, they should contact the profile owner and/or contact Fast Pitch! directly to have the logo removed. 

**Information Sharing**

**Sharing Information With Third Parties:**  
Fast Pitch! takes the privacy of our users very seriously. We will only share your personally identifiable with third parties to carry out your instructions and to provide specific services. For instance, we use a credit card processing company to bill users for subscription fees. These third parties do not retain, share, or store any personally identifiable information except to provide these services and are bound by strict confidentiality agreements which limit their use of such information.  
Fast Pitch! offers a “public profile” as well as Search Engine Optimization (SEO) features which publish portions of user’s profiles, including “name” and ‘company name’, to the public Internet. Users may opt-out of this feature, however Fast Pitch! does not warrant how third-party search engines will update their cache.  
We may provide aggregated data about the usage of our services to third-parties for such purposes as we deem, in our sole discretion, to be appropriate. We may segment our users by role (i.e. product managers, vice presidents), industry, geographic location, company. If you would like to be excluded from the aggregated research or products based upon aggregated data about our users’ activities on the site, please email customer service.

**Partnering with Other Organizations to Offer Combined Services:**  
Fast Pitch! may partner with other online services to give you the combined results of both services. Whenever we offer such combined services it will be your choice to make use of the combined services or not.

**Communications Between Users:**  
Many emails you initiate through Fast Pitch!, an invitation sent to a non-user for instance, will list your name in the header of the message. Emails you initiate may also provide aggregate information about your network and your company. Other communications that you initiate through the Fast Pitch!, like a request for contact, will list your name as the initiator but will not include your personal contact information. Your contact information will only be shared with another user if both of you have indicated that you would like to establish contact with each other. Some basic contact information will be provided to our ‘Platinum Users’ to allow them to have a better understanding of who is visiting their profile (i.e. See Who Recently Visited My Profile’).

Fast Pitch! merely provides the User with a platform on which to establish contact with other users, and only provides those technical applications that allow users to contact one another. As regards content, Fast Pitch! does not take part in any communication between users. If users enter into agreements with one another over Fast Pitch! websites, Fast Pitch shall not be a contracting party to these agreements. The users alone are responsible for the execution and/or fulfillment of agreements in which they enter with one another. Fast Pitch! shall not be held liable if users are unable to contact one another over Fast Pitch! websites regarding such agreements. Furthermore, Fast Pitch! shall not be liable for breaches of duty in relation to agreements entered into between users.

**Point and Rating System**  
Fast Pitch uses a credit and rating (‘stars’) system. You may be awarded credits based upon your status within the system (Premium Member, etc…) and/or your use of the system. Fast Pitch! may adjust your credit balance or rating, change system credit values or modify the credit and rating system at any time at its discretion. Credits have no monetary value and are not redeemable.

**Legal Disclaimer:**  
It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information when required by law. We will disclose such information wherein we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on our company or to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

**Accessing and Changing Your Account Information**  
You can review the personal information you provided us and make any desired changes to the information, or to the settings for your Fast Pitch! account, at any time by editing the information on your Profile page. You can also close your account through the Fast Pitch! website. If you close your Fast Pitch! account, we will remove your name and other personally identifiable information from our publicly viewable data. We may retain certain data contributed by you if it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally-identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law. All retained data will continue to be subject to the terms of the Fast Pitch! Privacy Policy that you have previously agreed to. To request that we close your account and remove your information from the Fast Pitch! service, please send your request to info@fastpitchnetworking.com. Please send your request using an email account that you have registered with Fast Pitch! under your name. You will receive a response to requests sent to info@fastpitchnetworking.com usually within a few days of the receipt of the email.

**Security**  
In order to secure your personal information, access to your data on Fast Pitch! is password-protected, and sensitive data (such as credit card information). At the present time, we do not have access to any detailed credit card information (unless provided directly over the telephone or at one of our events), as that is hosted entirely through our third party merchant service gateway ‘Cybersource, Inc.’. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
Fast Pitch! may update this privacy policy. In the event there are significant changes in the way we treat your personally identifiable information, we will display a notice on this site. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

**  
Questions or Comments**  
If you have questions or comments about this privacy policy, please email us at info@fastpitchnetworking.com or contact us at:

Fast Pitch! Brands, LLC  
Attn: Privacy Policy Issues  
6580 Palmer Park Circle  
Sarasota, FL 34238
